下载所有的数据能够降低延时并且最大化
Pulling down all the data will reduce latency and maximize the
利用电池效率。但是用户通常不会阅读所有的
battery efficiency. But it's unlikely the user is going to read every
文章。所以你浪费了很多带宽。下载
article. So you'd just be wasting a lot of bandwidth. Downloading
所有文章而不下载图片实际上是不会帮助我们提高效率的，
all the articles without pictures actually doesn't improve our efficiency if
比如你只是下载头版，因为当一篇文章被点开时
you're just downloading the front page, because you'll still need to
你仍然需要启动网络连接来下载图片
activate the radio to download those pictures whenever an article is
正确答案是下载首页所有的标题以及
selected. The right answer is to get the headlines and the
其对应的文章包括图片，因为它们是最有可能
articles linked to from that front page, 'cause they're the most likely
在用户打开APP后被读到的。
to be read as the user starts
之后你可以在用户移动到
browsing through the app. You can then incrementally
未进行预读的页面时
download more articles each time the user moves
逐步下载更多的文章
into an area you haven't pre-fetched for yet.